http://www.quikrete.com/contactus/privacy.asp

HOME
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
Table of Contents:
1. Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To protect the privacy of the visitors to the QUIKRETE® website at www.quikrete.com (the “Site”), QUIKRETE® Holdings, Inc. has developed this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this Policy easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested or submitted. Please read below for more specific information on the type of information that we collect and how we use it.
2. Types of Information We Collect
The information collected through the Site is voluntarily submitted by you. We do not utilize cookies to track your use of the Site. We do not collect the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet. We collect only information that you voluntarily submit to us, including but not limited to when you enter comments or questions through the Contact Us link on the Site.
If you choose to contact us, we collect your name, email address, and your suggestion or customer service request, along with any of the following information that you would like us to have in order to respond to your request: company, address, telephone number, facsimile number. We will not disclose to third parties any of the information provided by you to us without your permission other than as required by law and to comply with a court order or other legal process.
3. How We Use the Information We Collect
We will not disclose to third parties any of the information provided by you without your permission. We use the information obtained when you contact us through the “Contact Us” link to process your suggestion or customer service request in order to provide you with information regarding the products and services we offer. We also will use this information to improve our products and services.
You may, through our Site, submit information about other people and compose personalized messages to them. We will not use or disclose any information you provide about someone else for any purpose other than to send the communication to the person indicated, to identify or resolve technical problems or customer service issues, or as required by law and to comply with a court order or other legal process.
4. Other Information Collected
We may from time to time contract with advertisers or other third parties who place information, advertisements, or other promotional material or links on our Site. If you click on an advertisement or other link provided by a third party and leave our Site, whether through a link or through visiting another website framed within our Site, you are subject to the privacy policies of these advertisers or other third parties. We do not have responsibility for or access to the information collected by these third parties.
5. Our Commitment To Data Security
The security of all information associated with our users is an important concern to us. We exercise care in providing secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers. No sensitive data is stored in the pages directly. We have further measures in place to protect your personal information once it reaches us. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet, therefore you transmit to us at your own risk.
6. Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement at our home page located at www.quikrete.com. Private Policy – CA
7. How to Contact Us
For other information or questions regarding changing information that we have about you, please contact us at 1-800-282-5828 or send us an email to technical@quikrete.com.
